北达科塔
North Dakota.
我们可以一起做到
We can do this together.
自由这个词里可没有我
There is no I in freedom.
自由不是私域
Freedom is not medom.
而是群域
It's wedom.
我去了康涅狄格州Hartford的一家舞蹈工作室
I visited a dance studio in Hartford, Connecticut.
我在那碰到了一个坐在轮椅上的勇敢的消防员
When I was there, I met a brave firefighter in a wheelchair.
那个年头我们可不知道HIV阳性是什么意思
Back then, we didn't know what HIV positive was.
也就是说他失去了他的肾脏
Which meant he had to lose his kidney.
他握着我的手说
He shook my hand and he said,
你不记得我
You don't remember me,
但我是你的祖父
but I am your grandpa.
俄亥俄的下一任州长
The next governor of Ohio,
Roger Furlong.
我铺好了 你上吧 去你的吧
- I fluffed 'em, now go fuck 'em. - Shove it.
所有在场女士请说自 自
- All the ladies in the house say free. - Free!
所有在场男士请说由 由!
- All the men in the house say dom. - Dom!
谢谢!谢谢!
Thank you! Thank you!
喔 这可真令人惊讶 对吧?
- Wow, this is amazing. - Right?
像欢乐的纽伦堡 (二战纳粹审判地) 我知道
- It's like a happy Nuremberg. - I know.
红海到哪儿去了? 那位女士刚把它给分开了 (圣经故事 摩西事迹)
Where'd the Red Sea go? That lady just parted it.
嘿 总统得知道这个 因为Meyer现在可火了
Hey, POTUS needs to know about this 'cause Meyer's on fire.
我们刚失去佛罗里达的第三 第五和第六选区
We just lost the Florida third, fifth, and sixth.
很好 退休歹徒的选票是没戏了
Great, so much for the retired mobster vote.
佛罗里达...就应该把它在Jacksonville分开
Florida... ought to break it off
南边全分出去给古巴
at Jacksonville and row it to Cuba.
先生 西海岸投票后的民意调查看起来不太好
Sir, the West Coast exit polls are looking bad.
新英格兰呢
What about New England?
比政治行动委员会预测的最差结果还要糟糕 先生
Worse than the JPAC's worst projection, sir.
你正准备把一桶猪血浇我头上?
Are you getting ready to dump a bucket of pig's blood on my head?
唔 不 不 先生
Uh, no. No, sir.
谢谢 谢谢 先生 是的
- Thank you. Thank you, sir. - Yeah.
Dale 我很抱歉
Dale, I'm so sorry.
你不在参议院我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do without you in the Senate?
哦 他们...
Oh, they...
是的
Yeah.
是的 你败选了 Dale
Yeah, you lost, Dale.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
事实上 我被告知你已经知道了
And, actually, I was told that you'd been told.
对的 听起来你现在在公共场所 Dale
Right. Sounds like you're in a public place there, Dale,
所以你要去...你该深呼吸
so you got to... you got to breathe deep.
撑住 伙计
Hang in there, buddy.
我得挂了
I got to go.
我们刚丢了新罕布什尔的第一区
We just lost the New Hampshire first.
好吧 不错 每个人都讨厌我们
Okay, great. Everybody hates us.
你知道吗?我都打算开始讨厌我们了
You know what? I'm beginning to hate us.
我是说 这是总统的责任
I mean, this is POTUS's fault
因为 伙计们 我每次访问都出色地完成了任务 不是吗
because, guys, I killed it at every campaign visit, right?
没错 是那样 我女朋友说你超棒
Yeah, you did. My girlfriend said you are a rock star.
竞选活动里你的呼声很高
There was a lot of love for you on the campaign trail.
没错 很多支持者 不 不是说你 Marjorie
- Yeah, a lot of love. - No, not for you, Marjorie.
实际上 那可能是你失去新泽西第五选区的原因
In fact, that's probably why you lost the New Jersey fifth.
再见 你知道吗?
good-Bye. - you know What?
是时候让总统兑现他给我的选票承诺了
This is time for POTUS to start honoring his ticket promises to me.
我要我定期的一对一会面 喂?
- I want my regular one-on-one meetings. - Hello?
我要有更多权力
I want more responsibilities
在基础设施和教育改革上
in infrastructure and education reform.
在减少赤字的对话里我需要更多的话语权
I want an expanded role in deficit reduction talks.
我要一只卡地亚的人造阳具
I want a Cartier fucking dildo.
哦 嘿 Ame 你在听吗?
- Oh. - Hey, Ame, are you listening?
啊 是的 我妈妈刚打电话过来
Uh, yes. My mom just called.
我爸可能中风了
My dad may have had a stroke.
哦 天哪 Amy 我很抱歉
Oh, my God. Amy, I'm so sorry.
他还能说话吗?
Is he speaking?
哦 他告诉我妈 他吃完那个
Well, he told my mom he felt worse that time
日本基佬的破生鱼后感觉更糟了
he ate gay Jap raw fish shit.
哦 Amy 那可是个好征兆
Oh, Amy, that's a great sign,
因为那是个很复杂的句子
because that's a very complex sentence.
唔嗯 除非他只是随口吐词
- Mm-hmm. - Unless he's slurring his words.
哦 这...
Well, it...
那么 你要去守着他吗?
so, do you need to go and be with him?
我妈说他在找我 但我姐妹在那
My mom said he was asking for me, but my sister's there.
哦 好的 说真的 如果你走进去
Oh, good. Seriously, if you walked in,
你能想象他压力得有多大吗?
can you imagine how stressed out he might be
然后质问你在这里干什么?
with like, What are you doing here?
这时候你不是该和副总统在一起吗?
Isn't it time that you'd be with the veep?
这该死的中期选举 不是该她扩大
It's the freakin' midterms and isn't she gonna take this opportunity
在白宫影响的时刻吗? 或者什么之类的
to expand her role in the White House? Or whatever he might say.
但如果你得离开 Amy 那么就去吧
But if you need to go, Amy, you should go.
不 我很好 我留在这 很好 很好
- No. I'm good. I'm here. - All right, good.
那么你听到我刚说什么了? 是的 卡地亚人造阳具
- So you got what I said before? - Yes, Cartier dildo.
我刚刚在想我爸 但现在没有
I was thinking about my dad, but I am not now.
你知道吗? Dana的爸爸做了膝盖手术然后...
You know what? Dana's dad had a knee operation and it was...
哦 天哪 Gary 别再说你的女朋友了
Oh, my God, Gary, stop going on about your girlfriend.
真的吗? 我说了很多次?
Really? Am I that bad?
是的 这就是你 Gary... Dana Dana Dana Dana
Yeah, this is you, Gary... Dana, Dana, Dana, Dana.
好吧 好吧 好吧 Sue 谢谢
Okay. Okay. Okay, Sue. Thank you.
好吧 第一件事 分工
- All right, item number - job share.
我们要一起面对危机 没错吧?
We are going co-POTAL, right?
很明显 总统的办公厅主任正让所有人写遗书
Apparently POTUS Chief of Staff's telling everyone to write their will.
那儿的气氛将会变得很残酷
The mood over there is gonna be pretty grim.
就像斯敦镇惨案,(集体自杀题材电影） 哦 你知道我要什么吗?
- Like Jonestown. - Oh, you know what I want?
我想要那只我造型师推荐的口红
I want that lipstick that my stylist recommended.
哦 迈阿密森伯斯特 没错
- Ooh, Miami Sunburst. - Yeah.
那么午夜两点时
So when it hits 2:00 A.M.,
我的双眼会是大屠杀 而嘴唇则是狂欢节
my eyes will say Holocaust, my mouth will say Carnival.
俄亥俄那里有谁有消息吗
Does anyone have anything on Ohio?
他妈的这网络
Or why this fucking Internet
为什么比我们的经济预测更不靠谱
is sketchier than our economic forecasts?
哦 那是因为你的笔记本用的还是垃圾视窗2000
Oh, that's 'cause your laptop is still running on Windows 2000 and shit.
好吧 这是刚从政治行动委员会中心来的
Okay, this just in from J-stat central.
我们拿到了犹他州的第七和第九区
We've got the seventh and ninth in Utah down.
Jonah之队会继续关注统计数据 好吗?
Team Jonah's gonna have that stat watch, okay?
你们来找我 吃点墨西哥烤玉米片看下数字 嗯?
You come to me. Have some nachos and numbers, huh?
今晚会有一架飞机将火车
Tonight there's gonna be a plane crash
撞向拥挤的高速路
shunting a train wreck onto a crowded highway.
那会冲击道琼斯指数么? 或许我该买点股票
Is this gonna hit the Dow? Maybe I should have bought stock.
为什么 你遇到金钱方面的问题了?
Why, you got money problems?
不是钱的问题
Not money problems,
而是来自金钱的挑战
money challenges.
那是Furlong吗?
Is that Furlong?
明尼苏达州 Danny Chung刚增加了他的赢面
Minnesota. Danny Chung just increased his margin.
要赌赌Chung花多久谈论他的战功吗?
Want to bet how long it takes Chung to mention his war record?
不
No.
来吧 100块赌他会在五秒钟以内开始
100 bucks says he drops it in the first five seconds.
之前我是如何为需要我的海外美国人服务
And I intend to serve you the way I served
我就会如何来为你们服务
the American people overseas when they needed me.
哦 无聊Chung 无聊的华裔
Oh, ker-chung, ker-ching.
全清 吔
Pay up. Yeah.
我需要一些正面的消息 好吗? 一些能提高士气的
I need something positive, okay? Something to boost morale.
在印第安纳州的Lake郡我们的投票人数领先
We're ahead on voter turnout in Lake County, Indiana.
什么?就这样?
What? That's it?
这个 还有这次大地震没波及旧金山
That and the big quake hasn't yet hit San Francisco.
好吧
Okay.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
副总统女士
Madam Vice President.
哦 我有些好消息
Well, I have some good news.
看起来... 嘿 我们的票数领先
- It seems... - Hey, we are ahead on voter turnout
在印第安纳州的Lake郡
in Lake County, Indiana.
J哥报告完毕
J-dog out.
很抱歉 副总统女士 你刚刚说?
I'm sorry, Madam Vice President, you were saying?
那正是我要说的
I was saying exactly that.
是的 那会让我们摆脱现在的困境
Yeah, that'll take the edge off this cornhole.
各位 请坐下
Everyone, please be seated.
继续保持这种干劲 好吗?嘿 Ben?
Keep up the good work. Okay? Hey, Ben?
Ben?
你借来了Selina的迈阿密森伯斯特吗 Sue?
Did you borrow Selina's Miami Sunburst, Sue?
没有 哦 天哪
- No. - Oh, my God.
Mike 你的电话在响 你能接一下吗?
- Mike, your phone's ringing. - Could you get it, please?
是晨间节目 她不会上的
It's the morning shows. She's not doing them.
这是Mike McLintock的电话
This is Mike McLintock's phone.
他让我告诉你等一下
He's asked me to put you on hold.
如果我没回话 那么你就知道答案了
If I do not return, then you've got your answer.
我打扰了你休息吗 Mike?
Am I disturbing your downtime, Mike?
让我休息会 我在逛eBay
Give me a break. I'm on eBay.
就这样? 不 是强奸警报
Is this it? Nope, it's a rape alarm.
就像她总需要那个一样
Like she's ever gonna need that.
我是指 她不难看 但她需要很多保全
I mean, she's not ugly, but she's got a lot of security.
交流是你的工作 Mike
Communications is your job, Mike.
我在一个财政黑洞里 好吗？
I'm in a financial hole, okay?
我买了不该买的东西 还无法摆脱它
I bought something I shouldn't have and I can't get rid of it.
你买了什么 一艘船
What Did you buy? - a boat.
那是个委婉语吗? 不 就是船
- Is that a euphemism? - No, it's a boat.
一艘他妈的漏水的船 没人有兴趣
It's a leaky fucking boat and no one's bidding on it.
别对我吼 Mike 我可没强迫你买船
Do not yell at me, Mike. I did not force you to buy a boat.
龙骨是裂的 我得把它停在干船坞
I have a cracked keel, I have to dry-dock it.
有个洞 而我甚至不知道他妈的在哪...
There's a bilge, which I don't even know where the fuck...
嘿 停止这个船的话题 麻烦
Hey, stop talking about boats, please.
有人能帮把手吗? 就一会
Can someone please help me out for a second? One second.
好吧 唔 那你的问题的解决方案是什么 Gary?
Okay, hmm, what is the solution to your problem, Gary?
哦 用另一只口红
Oh, use another lipstick.
喔 那简单 那我的问题的解决方案呢?
Wow, that was easy. What is the solution to my problem?
卖肾?
I sell a kidney?
你知道吗 你知道吗 珊瑚色腮红
You know what? You know what? Coral Blush.
那看起来会是一样 珊瑚色腮红
That's gonna look the same. Coral Blush.
呆那边吧
Stay over there.
Ben?
你在这干什么? 避开那些坏消息
What are you Doing in here? - getting away from The bad news.
只是试图自我调整
Just trying to realign myself.
你知道我想什么? 呃 唔
- You know what I'd like? - Uh-uh.
我想被低温冷冻起来
I'd like to be cryogenically suspended.
哦 然后在未来醒来?
Yeah, and then be woken up in the future?
不 永远沉睡 就那样沉眠
No, never wake up. Just stay suspended.
你喝醉了?
Are you drunk?
不 我只是沮丧
No, I'm just depressed.
没关系 瞧
All right, look.
我有个计划
I got a plan.
今晚开始我将担起更多的领导责任
I'm gonna take more of a leadership role on
以副总统的身份
as vice president starting tonight
我需要你的建议去开展行动
and I need your advice as how to set that in motion.
问Kent
Ask Kent.
Kent Davison?
是 他回来了 高级策划
Yeah, he's back. Senior strategist.
不要啊 是的
No. - Yeah.
你知道他两年前的策划了什么吗
Do you know what his strategy was two years ago?
你还记得吗?他让我和前夫维持婚姻关系
Do you remember that? He had me hang with my ex-husband
就像我们还是曾经那个正常和睦的家庭
like we were this normal, loving family.
他让我们一起去漂流
He made us go river rafting together.
Catherine长了寄生虫
Catherine got giardia.
而我得整晚听Andrew在河边
And I had to listen to Andrew bang that skank
弹他的破吉他
on the riverbank all night.
我对Kent说 你能用什么方法让我感觉好点吗?
I said to Kent, Can you make me feel good about this somehow?
然后你知道他做了什么? 他指向图表
And you know what he does? He points to a graph.
他是铁石心肠 没错 他的精液都是冰的
- He is cold. - Yeah, he's got ice in his semen.
没错 他什么时候回来
Right. When's he coming back?
哦 他已经回来了 什么?
- Oh, he's back. - What?
他已经躲在某个通风口了
He's already squirreled away in an air vent somewhere
和他该死的数据一起
with his fucking statistics.
哪儿?他的办公室在哪?
Where? Where's his office?
知道那张男人的肖像画吗?
You know that portrait with the guy
看起来像肥狼獾
who looks like a fat Wolverine?
就在那个左边 一个门的距离
It's just one door on the left from there.
不过等等 等等 等等 等等 什么?
- But wait, wait, wait, wait. - What?
你知道明天我身上会发生什么吗?
You know what's gonna happen to me tomorrow?
不知道
No.
我的好朋友总统 我兄弟会的哥们
My good friend POTUS, my Gamma Chi brother,
会召唤我去他的办公室然后给我看一把剑
is gonna summon me to his office and he's gonna show me a sword
他会让我把剑吞下去
and he's gonna tell me to take the sword
直到剑从我的屁股穿出来
and slide it down my throat until it comes out my ass.
Ben 某天我们将会为此大笑
Ben, one day we are gonna laugh about this.
最后一件事...
One final item...
虽然副总统很欣赏
although the vice president appreciates your offer
你们陈旧的点心和令人愉悦的对话
of stale pastries and pleasant conversation,
但她不会参加晨间节目
she will not be doing the morning shows tomorrow.
她是在抛弃一艘沉船 Mike?
Is she deserting a sinking ship, Mike?
那是和我的船有关的裂痕么? 真有趣
Is that a crack about my boat? Really funny.
你们这群人真搞笑 把你的船放eBay上卖
you Guys are hilarious. - Put your boat on eBay.
谢谢 你能在eBay上卖会沉的船么
Thank you. - Can you Put a sinking ship on eBay?
谢谢 你可以在上面卖任何东西
Thank you. - you Can Put anything on there.
没有任何担任参议员的经历
Has no track record as a senator.
我很有经验的 亲
I've been around the block, honey.
你看到有只口红在这附近吗 有吗?
You haven't seen lipstick lying around, have you?
哦 是的 在办公室里
Oh, yeah, it's in the office
你的氯硝西泮制剂和女用止痒粉的旁边
next to your Klonopin and feminine itch powder.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
猜谁回来了 不可能是Furlong
- Guess who's back. - Not Furlong yet.
你可以信任我和俄亥俄的人
You can trust me and the people of Ohio.
我想今晚会有很多惊喜
I think there's gonna be quite a few surprises tonight.
这不是那个世界上最惊悚的保姆宣传语么?
Isn't that the catchphrase of the world's creepiest babysitter?
说到惊悚 Kent Davison回来了
Speaking of creepy, Kent Davison is back.
Kent Davison?那个玩图表的左翼份子
Kent Davison? The Pol Pot of pie charts.
哦 那可是个无情的家伙 真是个好榜样
Wow, that guy is ruthless. A total inspiration.
Hey.
嘿 我知道你认为我的统计家们都是狗屎
Hey, I know you think my stat guys are bullshit,
但我们提前拿到了俄亥俄州长的结果
but we got early exits on Ohio gubernatorial
它们对你而言可不怎么样 Egan先生
and they are not good for you, Mr. Egan.
闭嘴 Dan Egan办公室
Shut up. Dan Egan's office.
你好 Dan 国会议员Furlong找你
Hello, Dan. I've got Congressman Furlong for you.
给你 先生
Here you go, sir.
在递给我之前把那玩意擦掉
Wipe that thing off before you hand it to me.
给 嘿 漂亮的男孩
- Here you go. - Hey there, pretty boy.
你知道他们在监狱里是 怎么称呼你这种人的吗? 蜜饯
You know what they call guys like you in prison? Sweetmeat.
我可没计划去监狱 议员
I have no plan to go to prison, Congressman.
他妈的 那是他吗?
Holy shit, is that him?
没人打算去监狱 傻子
Nobody plans on going to prison, dipshit.
可事情有时候就是会那样发展
That's just the way it works out sometimes.
(你丫完了) 我告诉你
You are fucked.
如果今晚的选举我输了
If I lose this election tonight
要会回国会监督委员会
and I'm back on that Congressional Oversight Committee,
你就有麻烦了 因为我不喜欢你上司的管理方式
your ass is toast because I don't like the way your boss runs things over there
然后你就会是个很脆弱的靶子
and you are a mighty soft target.
如果我得跟着你 Dan 我可以保证
If I have to come after you, Dan, I can promise you something.
你想留下来就得得准备好被人干屁股
You're gonna have to be prepared to be gay for the stay
因为你就要完了
'cause you're going down.
打起精神 伙计 你会没问题的
Chin up, buddy. You'll be fine.
张开嘴
Mouth open.
肥狼獾
Fat Wolverine.
哦 Kent
Oh, Kent.
副总统女士 看你 你完全回来了
- Madam Vice President. - Look at you, you're all back.
我看到他们把水槽和马桶拿走了
I see they took out the sink and the toilet.
让你的地儿宽敞了点
Made it a little roomier for you.
我可以用拳头打穿这堵墙 然后拍上总统的肩膀
I could punch through the wall and tap POTUS on the shoulder.
你想好你拍他肩膀
And what would you be tapping him on the shoulder
要干什么了吗?
about specifically, do you figure?
重新定位 真高兴你说了那个
Repositioning. - So glad to hear you say that.
我们想的是一样的 我的朋友
We are on the same page, my friend,
不论是就党派来说 还是就我自身而言
both in terms of the party and, of course, in terms of myself.
我现是不是就该问你一个问题了?
Am I supposed to ask a question now?
哦 当然 你想的话 问吧
Oh, sure. If you want. Fire away.
应该问什么问题呢?
And what would that question be?
哦 问题就是
Well, that question might be
你认为最好的新定位是什么
what do you think is the best reposition to take?
那么那个问题的答案应该是什么
And what would the answer to that question be?
那个问题的答案就在
And the answer to that question would be
你眼前
standing right in front of you.
答案就是某个人
The answer would be a certain someone,
或者我们该说 那个未被充分使用的人
shall we say, whose skills were not adequately tapped.
这个问题可够大的
That's some question.
那么 我们很好
So, we're good.
我们没问题
We're good.
棒极了 我真高兴我们有这个机会交流
Great. I'm so glad that we had this chance to connect.
我说真的
I really am.
我不认为我之前说得很清楚
I don't think I was actually very clear before.
不 我叔叔以前说过
No. - my uncle used to have this saying.
他对我说 亲爱的 如果你没在桌上
He used to say to me, Honey, if you're not at the table,
你大概就在菜单里
you're probably on the menu.
Kent 我不会被吃掉的
And, Kent, I will not be eaten.
为什么有人想要吃了你?
Why would anyone want to eat you?
你知道我现在不用竞选什么职位吧?
You do know that I am not running for office right now?
我 事实上就是副总统
I am, in fact, the vice president.
我对你的头衔没有争议 只是对你的角色有疑问 好吧
I wouldn't dispute your title. I might question your role.
要是你能在副总统进房间的时候站起来那就太好了
It would be great if you would stand up when the vice president enters a room.
哦 上帝啊 好吧 哦 上帝
- Oh, Lord, all right. - Oh, Lord.
这就好了 哦 放轻松 Kent
- There you go. - Oh, at ease, Kent.
我只是在找我的马克杯
I'm just looking for my mug.
是的 我喜欢这个宝贝
Yeah. I love this baby.
它能盛九杯咖啡 哦 哇哦
- It holds about nine cups' worth. - Oh, wow.
是的 如果起火了 这是我唯一会带走的东西
Yeah, it's the only thing I'd save if this building were on fire.
好吧 这真是段愚蠢的对话
Okay. This is such a silly conversation that we're having.
我正打算去和总统谈话
I'm gonna go talk to the president.
他睡了 他已经睡下了?
- He went to bed. - He's in bed?
那你就是哨兵了?
So that makes you the livewire, huh?
这个就没法结束 它不会结束
- This can't get out. - It won't get out.
各位 总统已经睡了
Everyone, POTUS has gone to bed.
让我们为他的梦成真而奋斗到
So let's make sure we make his dreams come true tonight
弹尽粮绝吧
by fighting until that last bullet.
你为什么不用第一颗子弹
Why don't you take the first bullet
把自己的头打爆?
and put it through your brain?
是的 先生
Yes, sir. Pfft.
我将会在这里
I'm gonna have more of a role
承担起更多的责任
in this administration.
哦 我刚处理了那些数字
Well, I just crunched the numbers.
我知道 你就是专门干那个的
I know. You're the numbers cruncher.
现在它们一点味道都没了
And right now they taste pretty bland to me.
那么 加点调味料吧
Well, salt and pepper 'em.
Marion 你仔细听着
Marion, listen very closely.
现在让副总统上你节目的难度
You have as much chance of getting the vice president on your show
和让你丈夫离开那个拉拉队员差不多
as you have of getting your husband to leave that cheerleader.
是的 Marion 我们都知道了 再见
Yes, Marion. We're all aware of that. Good-bye.
非常脆弱 他们是这么说的?
Touch and go? Is that what they said?
不 那可是经典之作 上面还有专门放鱼叉的架子呢
No, it's a classic. There's a mounting on it for a harpoon gun.
Richard 我说了不就是不
Well, Richard, if you hear me say no, that means no.
不
No.
你很擅长打那些记者的脸哈
You good slapping down those hacks?
我确实蛮享受的
I really do enjoy it.
感觉就像一气甩了我所有的前男友
It's kind of like dumping all my ex-boyfriends at once.
你前男友很多哈?
Oh, you got a lot of exes, huh?
嘿 宝贝 是Gary
Hey, dumpling. It's Gary.
不好意思没接到你的电话
I'm sorry I missed you.
只是我没找到她的口红而已
It's just I can't find her lipstick
我觉得有可能是从家里的Leviathan像里面掉出来了 (一种传说中的海怪)
and I thought maybe it fell out of the Leviathan at home.
同志们 Kent Davison回来了
Okay, folks, Kent Davison is back.
第一 我们要怎么办?
what are we gonna do about it?
第二 为什么是我在通知你们这件事?
Number two: why am I telling you this news?
第三 能不能请你他妈的把电话挂了
And number three: would you please hang up the phone
因为老娘是美利坚副总统
because I'm the fucking Vice President of the United States
老娘有话要说 我挂了
- and I have something to say. - I'm going.
我们现在需要想办法 这件事上把Kent拉到我们这边来
So now we got to figure out a way to get Kent on board
共同面对危机
with this whole co-POTAL thing.
跟他讲道理是讲不通的 就像跟
You can't reason with him. It'd be like explaining
科莫多巨蜥解释什么是Supertramp乐队一样
Supertramp to a Komodo dragon.
我不明白你说的是什么话
na: I don't know what those words mean.
Mike 你是不是正在发作动脉瘤什么的?
Mike, are you in the middle of some sort of aneurysm?
我们往回倒一下 好么? 好的
- Let's just wind back a sec, okay? - Yes.
你觉得Kent Davison不是好事?
You think Kent Davison is a bad thing?
好了
Okay. All right.
我强烈感觉
I have a very strong feeling
Kent会在我和总统之间造成隔膜
that Kent is gonna get in between me and POTUS,
就像是很厚的套套一样
like some sort of thick rubber condom,
而我必须要... 直通
And I have got to have... - Unprotected.
直通总统办公室
Unprotected access to the Oval Office.
嗯 Amy 你和他一起跑过竞选
Well, Amy, you were on the campaign trail with him.
我们应该怎么对付他? 呃 我 啊...
- How do we pop him? - Uh, I, um...
我猜... 啥?
- Well, I guess... - What?
嘿 是
Hey. Yeah. - Yeah? Yeah?
嗯? 嗯?
You have to go and see your dad.
你得去看你爸 呃 这可是中期选举
This is the midterms.
Amy 这也就是他娘的中期选举 去吧
Amy, it's the fucking midterms. Go.
谢谢
Thank... thank you.
这可是他娘的中期选举啊
It's the fucking midterms.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
好了 各位 正式结果出来了
Okay, everybody, it's official.
我们丢了... 我们丢了国会多数
We have lost... - We have just lost The House.
所以把所有的东西都放上车
So put everything on the wagons
把狗都毙了 因为我们刚他妈的丢了国会多数
and shoot the dogs because we have just lost the fucking House.
就是他说的这个 太好了!
- What he just said. - Yes!
啥? 什么?
What? - What?
我觉得就是这样了 我觉得这是我们大显身手的机会
I think this is it. I think this is our time to strike.
好吧 计划是这样 我先去尿个尿
Okay, here's the plan. I'm gonna go pee pee
然后我们就把Kent灭了
and then we're gonna neutralize Kent.
非常好
Very good.
是的 是的
Yeah. - Yeah.
嘿 Mike 抱一下吧
Hey, Mike. Give me a hug.
Ben大叔要退了
Uncle Ben's on his way out.
那是什么 Ralph Lauren?
What is that, Ralph Lauren?
男式的
For men.
嗯 味道不错
Well, that's a good scent.
议员先生 嘿 断背Egan
- Congressman. - Hey, Brokeback Egan.
失陪一下 你能不能 把那破玩意从我鼻子下面拿开?
Excuse me. Would you get that fucking thing out from under my nose?
我可以 呃...
I could, uh...
我只是想就您竞选州长失利
I just want to offer my sincere condolences
致以真诚的慰问
on the loss of your gubernatorial race.
去你丫的 你去舔菊吧 Dan
Screw you and the face you rode in on, Dan.
噢 还有慰问您失去委员会主席的职务
Oh, and on the loss of your committee chairmanship, sir.
你要知道 我们现在失去了国会多数...
You know, now that we lost the House...
我们丢了国会你还在得意?
We just lost the House and you're crowing?
你为这个感到高兴么?
You're actually pleased about this?
为什么? 因为...我们丢了国会显然不是好事
Why? Because... well, we lost the House, that's bad, obviously,
但这样你就不用伺候我了 而这就好了?
but now this gets me off your case and that's okay?
我都没您说得清楚 先生
Couldn't have put that better myself, sir.
你是在吃我的批萨么?
Are you eating my pizza?
没有 先生 您...因为您刚才说...
No, sir, you... because you said that...
不 我说的是别在我面前晃
No, I said don't wave it in my face.
可没说让你吃 现在还能吃
- I didn't say eat it. - It's still good.
吃了它 马上吃光! 对不起
- Eat it! Eat it all right now! - I'm sorry.
我尽快赶过来了
Got here as soon as I could.
很高兴你能百忙之中来看老爸
Just really glad you could fit your father into your busy schedule.
她就是问句好 亲爱的
She means hi, honey.
Uh...
为什么他的心脏监视器没有亮?
Why is this heart monitor not on?
我没事
I'm fine.
他们不知道这是不是中风
They don't know if it was a stroke or not, hon.
好吧
Okay.
你说的是爸爸要临终了
You said Dad was dying.
对不起让你失望了 Amy
Well, I'm so sorry to disappoint you, Amy.
大喊大叫可没什么好处
All the shouting certainly isn't helping anything.
是啊 别喊了 Sophie
Yeah, stop shouting, Sophie.
我的天 Amy 你只是为副总统工作而已
Oh, my God, Amy. You work for the vice president.
又不是谷歌什么之类
It's not like it's Google.
Dan 什么?
Dan. - Yeah?
我尿完了 是的 女士
- My pee pee is done. - Yes, ma'am.
我们去收拾Kent吧 好了 J哥新闻
- Let's go crack Kent. - Okay, J-dog update.
我的天 他妈的大鸟来了
Oh, God. It's fucking Big Bird.
咱们从这边走
Let's go through here.
Oh!
哇哦 对不起打扰了
Whoa. - Sorry to disturb.
不知道你们在做什么 不过我会让你们接着做的
Don't know what you're doing, but I will leave you to it.
嘿 副总统女士
Hey, Madam Vice President.
你找到我的手下了 这是Jonah之队
I see you've found my crib. This is Team Jonah.
这是我的火热统计三件套 我的数据之源
This is my hot stat three-piece, my data Nirvana.
副总统女士 很荣幸见到您
Madam Vice President, it is such an honor to meet you.
非常感谢 我对你们在这个非常糟糕的夜晚
Oh, thank you so much. I really appreciate all the work you're doing
所做的一切感到非常感激
on this terribly depressing evening.
对您来说并不糟糕
Actually, not terrible for you.
您的助选总是让候选人们的支持率猛增
Your campaign visits always lead to a bump for the candidate.
什么? 您表现一直在水准之上
What? - you have been a consistent integer.
我不太确定我还记不记得什么叫水准
I'm not really sure I remember what an integer is, per se.
您就是好消息 您的表现都超过了总统
You're great news. You even aced POTUS.
您就像是Neo 哇
- You're like Neo. - Wow.
Neo是什么玩意? 他是黑客帝国里面的
- What's a Neo? - He's from The Matrix.
他干的事都巨牛
Everything he does is awesome.
只限第一集 续集糟透了
The first movie. The sequels sucked.
同志们 我们说过不争论黑客帝国的事了的
Guys, we agreed to let The Matrix debate lie.
天哪 我感觉我的童贞都长回来了
Jesus, I can feel my virginity growing back in here.
你是说所有这些数字对我来说都好么?
So you're saying that all of these numbers are good for me?
是非常好 好极了
- They're great for you. - That is outstanding.
Shh!
你能帮我很快对照一下发给我么?
Could you collate this for me very quickly?
完全没问题
Signed, sealed, delivered.
好了 和我在Kent办公室汇合 好的 一定
- Okay, meet me in Kent's office. - Yeah, absolutely.
哦 Kent Davison? 他和总统在办公室呢
Oh, Kent Davison? He's in the Oval Office with POTUS.
总统醒着呢? 据我所知是
- POTUS is awake? - Yeah, last I heard.
好吧 我会去总统办公室
Okay, I will be in the Oval Office.
会等着你给我那份材料
I will be expecting that material.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
那你想要什么格式的?
So what format do you want this in?
Excel? 饼状图?
Excel? Pie charts?
用英文就好
Just, like, in English.
你这是种族歧视梗么?
Is that a racist joke?
是的
Yeah.
快啊快啊快啊
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Amy Amy Amy 噢 谢天谢地
Amy, Amy, Amy. Oh, thank God.
怎么了? 听着 Amy
- What? - Listen, Amy.
副总统肯定出问题了
Something has happened to the vice president.
我知道你父亲快不行了 我非常非常的难过 Amy
I know your dad is dying and I'm really, really sorry, Amy,
但是我想Dana拿了Selina的口红
but I think Dana took Selina's lipstick.
这是Selina唯一开口要的东西
It's the one thing Selina asked for
而我手上没有 这毁掉了她的夜晚
and I don't have it and it's ruining her night.
好吧 你穿着胸罩好了 我会去你那边取口红的
Fine, keep your bra on. I'll swing by your place and pick it up.
谢了 听着 我有两个方法可以让她
Thank you. Listen, I've got two options I can offer her
弥补这个 然后我们就可以...好吧 太好了
as a stopgap and then we can... Okay. Oh, great.
爸 我很快就回来
Back soon, Daddy. Mwah.
希望你们CVS超市的老板不会介意你请假
Hope your boss at CVS is okay with you taking time off.
总是要最后说一句 你就是因为这样才单身的 男人可讨厌这样了
Always with the last word. That's why you're single. Guys hate that.
你和两个男人生了三个孩子
You have three kids by two different guys.
也许你最后一句话应该说不
Maybe your last word should have been no.
Kent.
总统在哪?
Where's the president?
在睡觉
Asleep.
那你应该在这吗?
Well, should you be in here?
人们需要相信他在这里指挥局势
People need to think he's in here leading.
可他没有
But he's not.
根据我散布出去的谣言 他在
He is, according to the rumor I put out.
好吧 我不在这
Well, I'm not in here.
不过既然我在这了
But since I am here,
我认为我们也许可以达成协议
I thought maybe we could agree
在任何有我 你还有总统
that at any joint meetings
的联席会议中
that you and I have with the president,
我应该第一个到最后一个走
I will be first in and I will be last out.
好吧 但是作为高级策划 我会提前到场
Fine, but as senior strategist, I'll already be in the room.
你是在暗示高级策划
Are you suggesting that a senior strategist
的地位要比副总统还高么?
is a higher position than a vice president?
这就要看副总统的了 是么?
It depends on The Vice President. - Yeah?
这个副总统就是我 而老娘他妈的超级棒
Well, this one is me and I'm fucking great.
而你不是民选代表
And you're not an elected representative.
你只不过是一个附属的民选代表
You're only an elected representative by default.
美国人民选的是他
The American people voted for him.
而他选择了我 知道么?
And him chose me, okay?
我要第一个出场
I'm gonna be in the room first.
最后一个出门
I'm gonna be in the room last.
你觉得这有得讨价还价么?
You think this is a negotiation?
你觉得你有什么资本来谈?
What leverage do you think that you have?
噢 我有资本
Oh, I have leverage.
我来的时候带了一大袋资本呢
I got a big bag of leverage coming my way.
那 副总统 总统...砰
So, vice president, president... bam.
少来了 你是副总统
Come on, you are the vice president.
从定义上来说 你就比总统矮半截
By definition, you should be at half the height of the president.
嗯哼 你想知道你在哪么?
Mm-hmm. You want to see where you are?
嗨 Kent 你好啊
Hi, Kent. How's it going?
谢谢你给我们把集会的备忘录带过来
Thank you so much for bringing us the memo on aggregates.
你怎么不去和自己的菊花来一炮呢?
Now why don't you just go and fuck yourself in your own asshole?
你到底想他妈干嘛?
What the fuck do you want?
女士 你要的东西来了
Ma'am, we have that data you requested.
噢 是的 进
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Come.
这里电视开着么? 没有 进来吧
- Was there a TV on in here? - No. Come in.
你可能想要坐着听
You might want to sit down for this.
没事的 我很好 好 说吧
- It's okay. I'm all right. - Okay. Hit it.
在成功助选方面 女士
When it comes to successful campaign visits, ma'am,
您领先总统0.9%
you have a lead over POTUS of 0.9%.
是啊 不过
Yeah, but that's not
这连百分之一都没有...
even a percent-age.
不过要是四舍五入的话 可以算成一个点的
If we round it up, we can make it one.
我找不到... 你就...
- I couldn't find... - Just...
先生 她用处很大
Sir, she has strong utility
还有坚实的选民基础...
and key demographics...
职业妇女 西裔选民等等
working mothers, Hispanic voters.
她吸引了摇摆选票 是的
She gives us traction in swing votes. - Yeah.
她是个有用的工具 不不不
- She's a useful tool. - Oh, no, no, no.
我不会再被当傀儡利用了 朋友
I'm not gonna be used as a prop again, my friend.
噢 女士 我永远也不会忘记
I will never forget on election night
你把我和我前夫放到台上的那个选举夜
how you put my ex-husband up on that stage
那是我的夜晚 Kent
and it was my night, Kent.
那是美国人心中的治愈时刻
It was a healing image for America.
你利用Catherine让事情看来
The way that you used Catherine to make it look
就像我们都团结在一起一样
as if we were all coming together.
冷静 你不许让我冷静!
- Calm down. - Don't you tell me to calm down!
我看见你办公室里
I saw that photo that you had in your office
她的照片上额头上写了浆糊两个字
with the word glue written across her forehead.
我要说水泥是不是会好点呢? 这里有好口红
- Better if I said cement? - Here's some good lipstick.
去他娘的口红!
Fuck that lipstick!
Kent? 你没事吧 对不起
Kent? Are you okay? I'm so sorry.
什么 你是不是嗑药磕高了 不不 她没有
- What, are you high? - No, no, she's not.
不 那是我的错
No, that was my fault.
呃 出什么事了?
Um, what's going on?
我刚见了总统
Just been with the president.
他让我留下来
He's asked me to stay on.
我的眼睛好痛
My eye hurts.
地毯上的那都是些什么?
What's that shit all over the carpet?
噢 我去 哦
an: Oh, shit. Ooh.
放点白酒醋的话 一擦就掉
If you have some white wine vinegar, that'll get it right out.
什么?
What?
白酒醋能擦掉污渍
White wine vinegar will lift the stain.
你收拾起眉眼
You take your eyebrows
给我滚出去 给您 女士
- and you get out. - Here, ma'am.
我有湿巾 我有很多湿巾
I've got some wipes. I've got a lot of wipes.
看这边 这边也有
Look right here. It's over here, too.
女士 不要! 你踩到别处了! 不要不要不要!
- Ma'am, no! You're tracking it! - No, no, no, no!
什么? 别这样
- What? - Don't do that.
就在你鞋跟上下不去
It's stuck on the bottom of your shoe.
等等 我能放下来这只了么? 干净了么?
Wait, do I put this one down? Is this clean?
等一下 回答我 是的
Wait a minute. just answer that. - Yes.
我的天哪 好了 把它从我鞋子上清掉
- Oh, my God. - Okay, get it off my shoe.
别擦 把鞋子给我就行 好吧 脱着鞋子
- Don't wipe it. Just give me the shoe. - All right, take the shoe.
你不应该在这里的 我们得走了 我知道
you should Not be in here. We need to go. - I know.
我们要跳一下 准备好了么? 一 二...开始跳
We'll do a little hop. Ready? One, two... there we go.
你得把这些收干净 会没事的
- You got to clean it up. - It's gonna be fine.
很多啊 可你做得到
- It's a lot. - You can do it, though.
好的 他可以的 好的
- an: He's okay, he's okay. - Okay. Okay.
我的天
Oh, God.
天 天
God, God.
Amy Dana 口红在你这么?
- Amy. - Dana, hi. Have you got the lipstick?
感觉像亲了副总统 很激动啊
Feel like my lips have touched the veep's. It's quite a thrill.
这可有点不尊重了
That's a little disrespectful.
嘿 Amy
Oh, hey, Amy,
我们不要一见面就不愉快 好么?
let's not start off on the wrong foot, okay?
我现在是Gary生活中很重要的一部分了
I'm a big part of Gary's life now.
而他很欢迎你
And you're welcome to him.
Amy 我想我们都知道那些见过他
Amy, I think we both know that any woman who's met him
却没能留住他的女人都会视我为敌
but didn't get to keep him is gonna see me as the enemy.
很抱歉 但是你已经错过了机会
I'm sorry, but you missed your chance.
我的苍天 我把口红弄干净了
Oh, my God. I got the lipstick out.
什么? 你在干什么? 那事不能有人知道
What? What are you doing? Nobody is gonna know about that.
Sue 总统打电话了么?
Sue, did the president call?
女士 他真打了 什么?
- Ma'am, he did, actually. - What?
副总统女士 哈?
- en: Madam Vice President. - Huh?
总统看到了你的0.9%
POTUS has noticed your .9%
他要在外交方面给你一个更重要的角色
and he's giving you an enhanced role
什么? 真的么?
in foreign policy. - What? Really?
所以 金正什么的
So, Kim Jong whatever
又开始甩他的核老二了
is swinging his nuclear dick again.
俄国人又往挪威人的什么鸟粪上插了旗
The Russians have planted their flag on a Norwegian pile of pelican shit.
你能给我发封电子邮件什么的吗?
Could you just send that to me in an e-mail or something?
你要和CENTCOM坐下来聊两个小时
You got a sit-down with CENTCOM in two hours.
什么?
What?
有几个美国背包客想跟不该惹的人
Some US backpackers tried to smoke a doobie
一起抽大麻 然后就在乌兹别克斯坦被绑架了
with the wrong dudes and they have been kidnapped in Uzbekistan.
乌兹别克斯坦就在土库曼斯坦还有另外一个
Uzbekistan is between Turkmenistan
我不在乎什么斯坦中间 376页上有地图
and I-could- give-a-fuck-istan. There's a map on page 376.
Kent.
我为之前的事情非常抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry about before.
不过天哪 你那声音太好玩了
Although, God, you made a funny noise.
我希望能把那个存成我的铃声
I wish I could get that as my ringtone.
那这个声音好不好玩 女士?
How's this for a funny noise, ma'am?
总统要你去做晨间节目
POTUS wants you to do the morning shows.
什么? 你会成为我们失败的代言人
What? - you will be The face of our failure.
不 不 Kent 我不能做那个 我累坏了
No, no, Kent. I can't do that. I'm exhaustipated.
你订了要上27个节目
You're booked for 27 interviews.
最好是涂点口红
Better put on some lipstick.
Wow.
我们输了一场战役 但是我们不会被驯服
We lost the battle, but we ain't cattle.
还有两年 贱人们!
Two years' time, bitches!
噢 天哪! 好吧 我有咖啡 有人参
- Oh, God. - Okay, I got coffee, I got ginseng,
还有蛋白质棒 你想要来点么?
I got protein bars. You want some of those?
不要 不要?
No. - No?
我需要瘾君子们用的那种东西
I need that stuff that junkies use.
就是那种吃了之后警察要开15枪才能打倒的药
You know, when it takes a cop 15 bullets to put him down.
我们离采访还有三分钟 女士
We have three minutes to the interviews, ma'am.
嘿 我在你的化妆台上找到的
Hey, I got this off your dresser.
你想戴着这根胸针么? 是的
do you want to wear this pin? - Yeah.
有一匹马从我头里出来了
There's a horse coming out of my head.
什么? 你在说什么?
What? What are you talking about?
那边...有匹马...
There. There's a horse...
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我都不知道为什么要我来管这些事
I don't know why I'm catching these things.
嘿 拿到你的口红了 我不想要他娘的口红
- Hey, got your lipstick. - I don't want the fucking lipstick.
她不想要他娘的口红 Amy
She doesn't want the fucking lipstick, Amy.
这个颜色更好
This color is better.
白宫希望能远离副总统的...事故
The White House wants to make sure
所以我们希望扔口红这种事
that they are kept out of the veep's incident,
发生在这里就好
so we want the lipstick throwing
别在总统办公室
to have taken place here and not at the Oval Office.
那是个意外 好么?
It was an accident, okay?
就像是大脚怪把你娘肚子搞大了 生下了你一样
Much like when Bigfoot got your mom pregnant, resulting in you.
这儿有什么事需要我的么?
Is there something I need to be in on here?
我是在说我的船
I was talking about my boat.
别了 Mike 你是在说他娘的船?
Please, Mike, you're talking about a fucking boat?
真的么?
Really?
我就要上砧板了
I'm about to enter a national ass-kicking contest
浑身带肉的
with no legs and a massive ass.
也没有那么多肉啦 女士 什么?
- It's not that big, ma'am. - What?
我觉得你的身材很完美
I think your ass is perfect.
早上好 奥克拉荷马城
Good morning, Oklahoma City.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
你想玩期中选举的无聊宾果么?
Want to play midterm cliche bingo?
她用的第一个词会是 我已经收到了起床铃
First phrase she uses. I already got wake-up call.
完全不是 我会说这是个坏消息
Not at all. I wouldn't say it's all bad news.
Frank 不 我不说这是次惨败
Frank, no, I wouldn't say it was a shellacking.
这不是场灾难 我是说 对我...
It's not a disaster. I mean, not for m-m...
对我来说不是...我是说...失陪一下
not for me... mean... excuse me.
嗯 我们晚上一直没睡
Well, we've been up all night.
美国人民给我们
The American people have said
敲了一记起床铃
this is a wake-up call.
我的天 我看起来好老
Oh, my God, I look so old.
不是
No.
你这算是什么反应?
What is that reaction?
你要用眼睛微笑
Smile with your eyes if you can.
好的 还要用上鼻子
Yep. - And your nose if you can.
用鼻子笑? 怎么弄
With my nose? How do you do that?
记得要谢一些人 好么?
Remember to thank somebody, okay?
别谢上帝 别扯到宗教
Not God. Don't make it religious.
要谢谢 呃...农民们 他们就爱这口
But thank, like, farmers. They love that shit.
大量么? 你刚才是这么说的吗?
Plurality? Is that what you said?
大...你看那个
Pulal... yeah, look at that.
大量 对
Plurality. - Yeah.
这样不好 你懂我意思吗?
It's not good, you know what I mean?
这个感觉有点像鱼的脸
It's kind of a fish face.
是的 是的 当然
Yes, yes, indeed.
这个嘛 有大量不同的看法
Well, there's been a plurality of views.
嗯 没有经济圣诞老人
Well, there isn't an economic Santa Claus,
我也没有希望有
and don't I wish that there were.
我们是美利坚合众国
Well, we are the United States of America
因为我们是合起来的大众
because we are united
而且我们在美利坚
and we are states
噢 我非常高兴 谢谢
and we are of America.
干得好 女士
Oh, it was my pleasure. Thank you.
结束了 结束了
ry: Oh, great job, ma'am.
把这个从我耳朵里面弄出去
- You're done. You're done. - Get this out of my ear.
咱们给您弄个舒服的椅子
Let's get you in a comfy chair.